(Amy:)Uh, mostly Penny's
heard them.
(Zack:)Boy, you get some
dirty looks over there
(Zack:)when you ask for ice.
(Raj:)Zack, this is
my friend Claire.
(Zack:)You're hot. You seeing anybody?
(Raj:)Uh, she's seeing me.
(Zack:)Why'd you say she's your friend?
(Raj:)We're just
keeping it casual.
(Zack:)Why is he being casual with you?
You seem great.
(Claire:)I don't know. Ask him.
(Zack:)Why are you being casual
with her? She seems great.
(Leonard:)Maybe we should
take a step back.
(Howard:)Take a step back?
I'm not a young man anymore.
(Leonard:)No, I mean reevaluate what we're
doing with the guidance system.
But (chuckles) I got a baby
on the way.
(Howard:)I got to make some money.
(Leonard:)What good is
money gonna do
(Leonard:)if we inadvertently
bring about Armageddon?
(Howard:)Okay, let me stop you
right there.
(Howard:)We absolutely know
(Howard:)our invention will not be used
to destroy the world.
(Bernadette:)How?